=Seal of Love= (Season 1)
= ختم الحب = (الموسم الأول)
=Episode 23=
= الحلقة 23 =
♪In regret someone's no longer happy♪
♪ مع الأسف لم يعد أحدهم سعيدًا ♪
♪I'm lost where we met♪
♪ ضاع حيث التقينا ♪
♪Our first meeting♪
لقائنا الأول
♪Was sealed by time♪
كانت مختومة بالزمن ♪
♪Who can I tell♪
♪ من أستطيع أن أقول
♪I miss you so much♪
♪ اشتقت لك كثيرا ♪
♪When I'm all alone♪
♪ عندما أكون بمفردي
♪You and I wish for something♪
♪ أنت وأنا نتمنى شيئًا ♪
(Stay away!)
(ابق بعيدا!)
♪When memories appear♪
عندما تظهر الذكريات ♪
Tomorrow, I'll hunt a hare for you,
غدا ، سأصطاد أرنبا من أجلك ،
(to reward you for watching fireflies with me.)
(لمكافأتك على مشاهدة اليراعات معي.)
(Aren't you scared?)
(ألست خائفة؟)
I am.
انا.
But I'm more scared of you getting hurt.
لكنني خائف أكثر من تعرضك للأذى.
♪Everything changes♪
♪ كل شيء يتغير
♪Bit by bit in a few nights♪
♪ شيئًا فشيئًا في بضع ليال ♪
♪I watch the stars flicker♪
♪ أشاهد النجوم تومض
This is half the antidote to the Soul-eating Sorcery.
هذا هو نصف ترياق لسحر أكل الروح.
Complete another mission
أكمل مهمة أخرى
(and you'll get the other half.)
(وستحصل على النصف الآخر.)
♪Letters by letters♪
حروف بحروف ♪
♪I weep as I write♪
أبكي وأنا أكتب ♪
♪Flowers and plants fade♪
♪ الزهور والنباتات تتلاشى ♪
♪In declining years♪
♪ في سنوات الانحدار ♪
♪Where will you be♪
♪ أين ستكون ♪
♪Can you take a look back♪
♪ هل يمكنك إلقاء نظرة إلى الوراء
♪Just one look♪
♪ نظرة واحدة فقط ♪
You let go of Meng Fusheng!
تركت منغ فوشنغ!
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Give me a reason.
أعطني سببا.
Sorry,
آسف،
I failed.
فشلت.
Humph.
همف.
You failed?
أنت فشلت؟
Yuan,
يوان،
you're my favorite disciple.
أنت تلميذي المفضل.
You never failed before.
أنت لم تفشل من قبل.
Never take a risk anymore.
لا تخاطر بعد الآن.
I did that for you.
لقد فعلت ذلك من أجلك.
Not even for me.
ليست حتى لي.
Yuan.
يوان.
Yuan?
يوان؟
Happy?
سعيدة؟
What's wrong, Happy?
ما بك يا سعيد؟
Do you know where Yuan is?
هل تعرف أين هو يوان؟
Beat him up
أوسعه ضربا
until he confesses!
حتى يعترف!
Yes.
نعم.
Happy, where are you going?
سعيد الى اين انت ذاهب؟
(Where am I?)
(أين أنا؟)
Meng Fusheng,
منغ فوشينغ ،
it's been so long.
انها كانت طويلة جدا.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
The one who will kill you.
الشخص الذي سيقتلك.
Do I know you?
هل انا اعرفك؟
Qing Chen has been deceived
لقد تم خداع تشينغ تشن
by your innocent face.
من وجهك البريء.
You chose to forget things again and again
اخترت أن تنسى الأشياء مرارًا وتكرارًا
but you leave everything
لكنك تترك كل شيء
to those who still have memories.
لأولئك الذين ما زال لديهم ذكريات.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
What did I forget?
ماذا نسيت؟
You want to know?
أنت تريدأنتعرف؟
Sorry, but not a chance.
آسف ، ولكن ليست فرصة.
I've been expecting this day
كنت أتوقع هذا اليوم
for quite a long time.
لفترة طويلة.
In the Immortal or Human World,
في العالم الخالد أو البشري ،
I don't want to hear your name anymore.
لا أريد أن أسمع اسمك بعد الآن.
Now, you're in my territory.
الآن ، أنت في أرضي.
I'd like to see
أود أن أرى
who can save your life.
من يستطيع أن ينقذ حياتك.
♪In the next life May everything be in peace♪
في الحياة الآخرة ، عسى أن يكون كل شيء في سلام
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪ العودة في مسقط رأس الهواجس باقية ♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love I just can't get over it♪
♪ أسعى وراء الحب النحيف الذي لا يمكنني تجاوزه
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪